



# **Core Competencies**

- Technical Support Engineer
- IT Support
- · remote desktop
- Software Support
- Troubleshooting
- Technical Analysis
- System Administration
- · incident management
- Project Coordination
- Manual Testing
- Web Testing
- · Functional Support
- · Leadership Quality



# **Technical Skills**

- Lambda Test
- Front End
- MICROSOFT



## Personal Information

Date of birth 22-May-1991

Gender Female

Address Pune, Maharashtra.

City Pune

Country INDIA

# Yogita Arun Bhosale

## **Technical Support Engineer**



6 years 0 month



9552497237



## "

Technical Support Engineer seeking roles in IT Support, Front end support, Manual Tester, Android/IOS Functional support, Project Co-ordinator, Technical Consultant, Software Support, Troubleshooting, Technical Analysis, Incident management.



## **Profile Summary**

Result-oriented Professional with over 5 years of experience in Software Support including Front end Support, Project Coordinator, Tech Consultant, Business Analyst, Functional Consultant, Technical Analysis, Troubleshooting, Manual Tester, Application Support, product Support Having Leadership Quality.



## Education

MS/M.Sc(Science), 2014

**Pune University** 

B.Sc, 2012

**Pune University** 



## Work Experience

Feb 2020 - Present

**Technical Support Engineer** 

#### Firstcry.com

Responsibilities:- Troubleshooting of on all Android/IOS app. Escalated the incident on different higher level to close it at the earliest. Responsible for handling technical Incidents related to certain specific products. Performing Regression testing for Android & IOS app testing. Experience in Mobile & Web Application. Making of all android, IOS app Incident Report related to specific version, Device Details and sharing it to all management on Daily Basis. Ticketing: Generate new Tickets, Update in previous Tickets. Try to close all technical tickets/Queries related to Desktop Site/App Site/Msite. Have hands on Experience for Project Tracking tools like Redmine. Having experience in Testing of different Payment Gateways and UPI payment technology. Execute Front end Functional Support Part. Good Experience in checkout flow like payment modes and payment gateways. Hands on Experience Functional Testing, Regression Testing, & Cross Browser Testing Desktop, MS, Android app, IOS app testing various versions of mobile device on Browser stack. Solve Technical issues of internal department through email. Co-ordination with Team Managers, Leads. Expert in Excel (VLOOKUP, pivots, formulas, charts, with full autonomy) Tools used: CRM Tools (Creating Trouble Ticket and managing Outages)

#### Mar 2018 - Nov 2019

**Technical Support Officer** 

#### PurpleRadiance Technologies Private Ltd.

Responsibilities: Troubleshooting of CDR Analysis Software. Responsible for handling technical Incident related to certain specific products like CDR, CellTrack Application and SDR Application. Clients: Leading Law Enforcement, Defence and National Security Organizations. Project Title: CDR Software support. Updation, Installation, Reinstallation, Activation of Software. Installation of dot net framework 4.7, Installation of database. Ticketing: Generate new Tickets, Update in previous Tickets. Remote Access of Team viewer/Anydesk to solve problems. Solve Technical issues of Clients through Online as well as Offline. Installation of ADE 32/64 bit and Winrar. Working through Multibatch Job abends. Application Startup and Shutdown. Responsible for handling Incident Management Monitor the Queue for events and raise necessary tickets File restorations. Work on trouble tickets as assigned by Onsite team lead and Provide required updates to onsite for all incidents and service calls. Ensure response & resolution or recovery of service ASAP after implementation of solution work around for cases. Perform L2 troubleshooting as the situation dictates for any and all network outages as reported by users and operational personnel. Coordinate with Onsite team to ensure timely and satisfactory resolution for any trouble tickets. Coordination with customers via call and Email to share that update and provide as surety for the earliest resolution. Escalated the incident on different higher level to close it at the earliest. Tools used: CRM Tools (Creating Trouble Ticket and managing Outages):- Service Now&First Project Title: CellTrack And SDR Application Application Startup and Shutdown. Initial diagnosis of faults- Validation. checking and validating Cellids value onto server and upload it periodically.

#### Oct 2014 - Sep 2016

QA Grade I

#### CREST(Part of Springer Nature).

Responsibilities:- Troubleshooting of Software. Solve coding problem of technologies like HTML5,CSS3,Xml. Execute Front end technologies coding part. Solve Technical issues of internal department through email. It is a final department of Quality Check and sends Packages to direct vendor on their Server. Co-ordination with Team leader Role: Quality Analyst G-I Responsibility:- Convert PDF Document into XML Files as per Client?s Requirement. There has been defined mechanism at Springer to control various aspect of Technical concern in books, journals and magazines.